Problem 1: Write a procedure that will transform a given string A (which contains only
uppercase or lowercase letters) in string B which contains only lowercase letters (each
uppercase letter will be replaced with a lowercase letter) and returns as a result the number of
replacements N done for the transformation. The procedure has one argument that represents
the effective address of string A and it should be passed through the register SI (the string starts
at address DS:SI). Note that the end of the string is marked with $. The output data N should be
returned through the stack.
In the main part of the application insert two strings via the keyboard and writhe them in the
memory (string have at most 50 characters and only uppercase and lowercase letters are
inserted). For the end of the string the sign $ should be inserted.
- Using the procedure transform the strings you inserted in strings that contain only
lowercase letters.
- In the variable transformations store the total number of replacements done in the
transformations for both strings.
- Finally, check if the two strings you inserted have the same length and that they
have the same letter (no matter if it is uppercase or lowercase letter) on each
position in the string. Write an appropriate message like in the examples given.
Example 1:
Enter string: cdAcmDFp$
Enter string: cdAcmаfp$
Output: False condition (transformations=4 since 4 uppercase letters were replaced with lowercase
letters)
Example 2:
Enter string: cdAcmDFp$
Enter string: CDaCMdfP$
Output: True condition (transformations=8)